Finding Aid for James Morgan Papers ca. 1900-1988
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
James Morgan Papers c.1900-1988 1950-1988
Morgan, James.
.5 linear ft.
Member of the Ann Arbor Township Planning Commission; minutes, correspondence, maps and photographs.
98104 Aa 2
Bentley Historical Library University of Michigan
The collection was donated by the Ann Arbor Kiwanis Club (donor no. 8712 ) in April 1998.
The collection is open for research.
James Morgan was a resident of Ann Arbor Township and a member of the Ann Arbor Township Planning Commission.
The James Morgan Papers include minutes, correspondence, maps and photographs. The collection is organized in three series: Ann Arbor Township Planning Commission, Personal, and Photographs.
Subjects:
Morgan, James.; Ann Arbor Township Planning Commission.
Subjects - Visual Material:
Butchershops--Michigan.; Railroad employees.
Genre/Form:
Photographs.
- Ann Arbor Township Planning Commission
  The Ann Arbor Township Planning Commission series contains minutes, correspondence and maps relating to the commission's activities in the late 1970s and 1980s.
  - Minutes, 1979-1985, 3 folders (Box 1)
  - Correspondence and Reports, 1981-1984 (Box 1)
  - Domino's Farm Phase II (Box 1)
  - Planning Material, 1984-1985 (Box 1)
  - Clippings, 1988 (Box 1)
  - Solent Acres, Ann Arbor Township; Planning Maps, 1949-1983 (Box 1)
- Personal
  The Personal series contains a memorial notice for William Morgan and a letter written by James and Margaret Morgan.
  - Personal letter and William Morgan memorial notice, 1960-1961 (Box 1)
- Photographs
  The Photographs series consists two folders of photographs taken or collected by James Morgan. The first folder contains photographs of Morgan's home, family, and vacations, probably in Northern Michigan. The second folder contains several tintype family portraits, a photograph of the Oscar Lamkin Meat Market in Lodi, Michigan, a photograph of an unidentified group of workers in a rail yard, and an unidentified photograph of a student musical revue.
  - Family and vacation photographs, c., 1945-1975 (Box 1)
  - Older family photographs, c., 1900-1930 (Box 1)